http://www.rjagroup.com/privacy

COVID-19 Update: Message from our CEO.
Read More
Search Our Site
×
Search input
It looks like you’re using an unsupported or outdated browser. For the best experience, please update or upgrade your browser.
Careers
Why Work Here?
Students + Graduates
Careers
Why Work Here?
Contact
The website is operated by and on behalf of Jensen Hughes - including its affiliates, divisions, business units and subsidiaries ("Company").To establish personal data protections, the Company has implemented a privacy policy that incorporates foundational privacy principles and concepts that support compliance with applicable privacy laws and regulations. This Privacy Statement summarizes how our policy applies to our website and related communications and services ("Services") but excludes services that state that are offered under a different privacy statement or policy. This Privacy Statement applies to personal information the Company may collect through this website, and to other information we may collect in the course of our business. The Company will determine the purposes and means of processing personal data provided to, collected by or for, or processed in connection with our Services. As either an Anonymous Visitor or a Registered User of our Services, the collection, use and sharing of personal data is subject to this Privacy Statement and updates. Jensen Hughes respects your privacy and does not sell, rent or loan any personal data collected. Any information that you give Jensen Hughes will be treated in a careful and secure manner and only for legal and authorized purposes consistent with this Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement does not apply to personal information relating to the Company's own employees. The collection, processing and handling of Company employees' personal information is governed by Company policies. Specifics of how personal data will be collected and administered is described below.What data do we collect?Data you provide usWe collect information from you when you fill out a form. When contacting us through our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, company name and/or job title. We collect data and process data when you:Register or complete a contact, or information request formVoluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback via emailUse or view our website via your browser’s cookiesFollow or connect with us via social media or the telephoneShared with us at events and trade showsRequest an interview with a Jensen Hughes spokespersonRequest a Jensen Hughes expertApply for a position with the CompanyIf submitting a Request for Proposal (RFP) or Forensic Assignment (FA)In addition to the data listed above, when submitting an RFP or FA, you may provide personal data on other individuals associated with the request. This information includes, but is not limited to:Insured’s information (name, address, phone number)Billing information (name, address, phone number)Loss location (address)Claim and/or evidence description, which may include names, addresses and phone numbersIf applying for a position with the Company, please be aware of the following:We collect personal data from you when you provide, post or upload a document to our site, such as when you fill out a form or submit a CV/resume.You have choices about the information on your applicant profile, such as your education, work experience, and skills. You should only include information relevant to job qualifications for our recruitment and hiring process. When you apply for U.S.-based positions, we are legally required to ask you to identify your race, ethnicity, gender, veterans and disability statuses. However, you are under no obligation to provide that information.Please do not upload or include Sensitive Personal Data in your profile, including your CV or other documents. Sensitive Personal Data may include, but is not limited to, racial or ethnic background, physical or mental health information, religious beliefs, genetic or biometric data, and sexual orientation.Data we automatically collectWe also collect data indirectly through the use of cookies, website analytics and through social media. Data may also be collected and stored based on your interaction and behavior with our website and email communications.How will we use your data?Our Company collects data to allow us to better service our clients and your needs. We collect the identified data to address our legitimate business interest in providing services to our customers and other interested individuals. This interest is not overridden by your personal interests, rights and freedoms in protecting your personal data. The personal data you provide may be used to:Communicate with you about our services, future events and updates about Jensen Hughes, in accordance with your communication preferences. Operate, evaluate, and improve our businessAnalyze our products, services, and websitesPerform market researchContact you during the recruitment and hiring processHow do we share your data?We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal data that you provide to us or that we collect, except as described here. We may share personal data you provide to us or that we collect through the website with service providers that perform services on our behalf (i.e., collections assistance). When we work with these service providers, we put in place appropriate confidentiality and security measures to limit the use of your personal data only for legal and authorized purposes that are consistent with this privacy statement.Is data transferred and how is it stored?We are a global company and will transfer personal data in a way that complies with the law wherever we transfer it. Personal data collected by Jensen Hughes may be stored and processed in the United States and our affiliates and subsidiaries in other countries. We will take all reasonable steps to safeguard the transfer of your personal data and ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.Our Company securely stores your data in the following ways:On secure web, email and data cloud hosting servicesOn internal servers and computers including laptopsOn mobile devicesThe Company will comply will laws and regulations related to retention and destruction of any personal data collected through our website. SecurityWe have reasonable and appropriate electronic and physical security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, no technology, data transmission or system is guaranteed or warranted to be 100% secure. Your data protection rightsAs our processing of your personal data is based on consent, you may at any time withdraw that consent provided that the withdrawal of the consent does not affect the lawfulness of the previous processing, or when there are other legal grounds for the company retaining your data as processed. In addition, under applicable data protection laws, you have the right to: (i) receive information on what personal data Jensen Hughes is collecting; (ii) receive access to such data and, if necessary, have it changed so it is correct; (iii) have your personal data deleted; (iv) restrict Jensen Hughes from processing, or limit the way we may process, your personal data; and (v) obtain a copy of the personal data we have collected.You may contact us by e-mail or as described in the “How to Contact Us” section below to exercise your rights described above.If you are in the European Economic Area, you can also withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the lawfulness of any processing conducted prior to your withdrawal or processing your personal data under other legal bases.You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority in your country. You can find the contact information of the data protection supervisory authority in your country here.If you are in California, you have a right to knowledge, access, and deletion of your personal data and will not be discriminated against for exercising a right under the California Consumer Privacy Act.CookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology.For further information, visit allaboutcookies.org.How do we use cookies?Our Company uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:Keeping you signed inUnderstanding how you use our websiteImproving the usability of our websiteTracking and analyzing web trafficWhat types of cookies do we use?There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:Functionality cookies: Our Company uses these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer and location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies are used.Session cookies: These allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browser session only, for example on amecfw.com a session cookie is used to remember the details a user provides when downloading images from our image library. This means that if the user downloads more than one image they only need to enter their details once during that session. Session cookies expire after a browser session i.e., as soon as you close the browser windowPersistent cookies: These are cookies which are stored on a user's device in between browser sessions which allow the preferences or actions of the user to be remembered. Jensen Hughes does not use these type of cookiesFirst party cookies: This is the general name for cookies which are set by the website visited by a userAnalytical cookies: These are cookies used to collection information about how people access and use a website and are the type mostly used on our site. How to manage cookiesYou can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.Privacy policies of other websitesOur Company website contains links to other websites. This Privacy Statement applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy statement.Updates to our privacy statementOur Company keeps its privacy statement under regular review and places any updates on this web page. We will post the updated version and indicate at the top when it was most recently updated. How to Contact UsUnsubscribe or Opt-outIf you would like us to update information we have about you or if you no longer wish to be contacted by Jensen Hughes, you may contact us:By email at info@jensenhughes.comOr send a written request to:Jensen Hughes3610 Commerce Drive, Suite 817Baltimore, MD 21227In addition, you may also opt out by using the unsubscribe option on an email.QuestionsIf you have any questions or comments about this Statement or any issue relating to how we collect, use, or disclose personal data, or, you may contact us:Corporate Compliance OfficerJensen Hughes, Inc.3610 Commerce Drive, Suite 817Baltimore, MD 21227compliance@jensenhughes.com
Featured Image
About Us
Find out more about who we are.
Read More
Featured Image
Contact
Want to get in touch?
Reach out
Featured Image
Global presence, local reach
We have more than 90 offices worldwide.
Contact a local office
Necessary (Required)
Cookies that the site cannot function properly without. This includes cookies for access to secure areas and CSRF security. Please note that Craft’s default cookies do not collect any personal or sensitive information. Craft's default cookies do not collect IP addresses. The information they store is not sent to Pixel & Tonic or any 3rd parties.
Name: CraftSessionId
Description: Craft relies on PHP sessions to maintain sessions across web requests. That is done via the PHP session cookie. Craft names that cookie “CraftSessionId” by default, but it can be renamed via the phpSessionId config setting. This cookie will expire as soon as the session expires.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Session
Name: *_identity
Description: When you log into the Control Panel, you will get an authentication cookie used to maintain your authenticated state. The cookie name is prefixed with a long, randomly generated string, followed by _identity. The cookie only stores information necessary to maintain a secure, authenticated session and will only exist for as long as the user is authenticated in Craft.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Persistent
Name: *_username
Description: If you check the "Keep me logged in" option during login, this cookie is used to remember the username for your next authentication.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Persistent
Name: CRAFT_CSRF_TOKEN
Description: Protects us and you as a user against Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Session
Details
Hide Details
